(Sheldon:)Mother, she's an atheist,
(Sheldon:)not a vampire.
(Mary:)Either way, let's stop
and get some garlic.
(Beverly:)So, Mary, how have you been?
(Mary:)Well, thank you
so much for asking.
(Mary:)I've been well, and you?
(Beverly:)Very good.
Good.
(Sheldon:)I don't know what
we were worried about;
they're getting along great.
(Mary:)Sheldon tells me
your husband's coming.
(Beverly:)My ex-husband.
(Mary:)Oh, I'm so sorry.
(Mary:)Don't be.
(Mary:)All right.
(Penny:)Whew, chilly.
(Amy:)I think I can see my breath.
(Beverly:)We can hear you.
(Leonard:)Sorry.
Sorry.
(Howard:)I can't believe I was so naive.
(Howard:)The military is just gonna
(Howard:)take over the whole project.
(Howard:)And you know what happens
if we object?
(Howard:)We disappear.